<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Microsoft &#8211; microbiablog</title>
	<atom:link href="/microbiablog/tag/microsoft/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/microbiablog/</link>
	<description>Cuanta maldad...</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 20:41:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Surface 3 killed my iPad (and is the coolest tablet ever)</title>
		<link>/microbiablog/tecnologia/surface-3-killed-my-ipad-and-is-the-coolest-tablet-ever/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 12:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[microbia]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tecnología]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[surface]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/microbiablog/?p=841</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Usually I don’t talk about Microsoft products, but after falling in love with my new Surface 3, I have to explain why is the coolest tablet ever With the launch of Windows 8, almost 3 years ago, I got a free Surface RT. Unfortunately the whole concept “RT” was a fail. “RT” meant that while [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/tecnologia/surface-3-killed-my-ipad-and-is-the-coolest-tablet-ever/">Surface 3 killed my iPad (and is the coolest tablet ever)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Usually I don’t talk about Microsoft products, but after falling in love with my new Surface 3, I have to explain why is the coolest tablet ever</h3>
<p>With the launch of Windows 8, almost 3 years ago, I got a free Surface RT. Unfortunately the whole concept “RT” was a fail. “RT” meant that while it looked like a regular windows 8 computer, you couldn’t install any desktop applications. Considering the App Store catalogue at the moment and the price tag I’m not surprised it didn’t succeed. Mine has been sitting in a drawer since then.</p>
<p><img style="background-image: none; padding-top: 0px; padding-left: 0px; display: inline; padding-right: 0px; border: 0px;" title="microsoft-surface-3" src="/microbiablog/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/microsoft-surface-3.jpg" alt="microsoft-surface-3" width="1000" height="500" border="0" /></p>
<p>This year I got one of the new basic Surface 3 (600 €) for testing purposes. This time it IS like a regular computer, you can install whatever desktop applications you want + there are a lot more apps in the store.</p>
<p>At home, when I’m not working, the iPad is with me most of the time. I don’t use a lot of apps, mostly: Flipboard, Mitele, Atresmedia, TV online, Youtube and Chrome. I use it to watch TV, flipboard and browsing the internet.</p>
<p>This summer I was planning to take my iPad with me on holidays. However, as I had been playing with it to test Windows 10, I thought, why not? Let’s take the surface to the beach. It’s pretty much the same size, slightly heavier, BUT it has an amazing keyboard and Office 2016 in case I need to work. And all the apps I need are also available in the Windows Store, so I won’t miss anything. And for the first time in a long time, I fell in love. I developed this type of bond you get with those gadgets you can’t live without, you get me right?</p>
<p>I have to say it doesn’t replace my work laptop. My surface is the basic version, with an Atom x7 processor, even though you can use it for Photoshop, you need to be aware it’s not a super powerful processor, and I usually have tons of tabs open at the same time, excel, visual studio… Even though it performs great for “average” workload, I don’t see you editing video or launching rockets with it. My iPad would start to scream as soon as I open several tabs in Chrome, there would be no way it could handle the same hassle.</p>
<h2>Surface 3 vs iPad Air 2 specs</h2>
<p><img style="background-image: none; padding-top: 0px; padding-left: 0px; display: inline; padding-right: 0px; border: 0px;" title="ipad-vs-surface-3" src="/microbiablog/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/ipad-vs-surface-3.jpg" alt="ipad-vs-surface-3" width="730" height="542" border="0" /></p>
<p><img style="background-image: none; padding-top: 0px; padding-left: 0px; display: inline; padding-right: 0px; border: 0px;" title="ipad-air-vs-surface-3-specs" src="/microbiablog/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/ipad-air-vs-surface-3-specs.png" alt="ipad-air-vs-surface-3-specs" width="634" height="562" border="0" /></p>
<h2>Killer Surface features</h2>
<p><strong>Keyboard</strong></p>
<p>One of the biggest reasons why it has overun my iPad, is the keyboard. Most people complain it sells separately at 150 € and I understand, but it is really worth it. The keyboard has real keys (you don’t type against something flat) and is a breeze to use.</p>
<p><img style="background-image: none; padding-top: 0px; padding-left: 0px; display: inline; padding-right: 0px; border: 0px;" title="Surface-3-2-730x487" src="/microbiablog/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/Surface-3-2-730x487.jpg" alt="Surface-3-2-730x487" width="730" height="487" border="0" /></p>
<p><strong>Connectivity</strong></p>
<p>The surface 3 has 1 USB 3 + Mini Display Port + microSD + standard microUSB port for charging. You don’t get any of those in an iPad, and this is where it gets tricky. When you use your Surface with the keyboard, you somehow forget it’s a tablet, and compare it with a laptop, like the Macbook Air, and of course that’s a battle where Surface won’t win, but we’ll leave that to the Surface Pro.</p>
<p>However, I see the basic Surface 3 doing an outstanding job and perfoming perfectly for most tablet and laptop users.</p>
[youtube vV4BImDSMF4]
<p><strong>Taking notes</strong></p>
<p>If you are a person who loves taking notes by hand, or drawing, or doodling while meetings, you will enjoy Surface. With an outstanding system to detect your hand and the pen strokes, artists and students around the world are raving about it.</p>
[youtube Va-eVYdh9GE]
<p>Yes, the pen is also sold separately (50€) but it’s one of the best stylus out there.</p>
<p><strong>Office 365 for free</strong></p>
<p>The basic surface comes with a preview of Office 2016 + 365 yr subscription. Combine the note taking capabilities with  OneNote super powers (another of my favorite products) and you get a killer notebook: easily take notes, record a meeting or class in video, share notes with other people and have it all sync with Dropbox or Onedrive, which means you can have it available in your mobile or other computer within seconds.</p>
<p>Of course if you are a professional who needs to edit spreadsheets, send word documents, generate PDFs… this is definitely your device.</p>
<p><img style="background-image: none; padding-top: 0px; padding-left: 0px; display: inline; padding-right: 0px; border: 0px;" title="surface-office" src="/microbiablog/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/surface-office.jpg" alt="surface-office" width="620" height="465" border="0" /></p>
<p><strong>External screen</strong></p>
<p>If you plan to use it as your desktop computer, you can easily do that by plugging an external screen to the mini Display Port. This is also handy if you make presentations as you can plug it to a projector.</p>
<p><strong>Windows 10</strong></p>
<p>Of course you can update to Windows 10 for free. I always hated the win 8 “metro” screen (the screen with tiles) I am a desktop person. Windows 10 gets rid of that screen and gives you the “regular” start button we have always loved. One more reason to update is you will not lose any of your installed apps, documents, settings… the upgrade is the easiest and smoothest ever. I didn’t even backup (my important stuff is in Dropbox, so in case anything is lost, I don’t care. I strongly recommend you backup if you have important stuff and you don’t have a copy.</p>
<p>Another reason is booting time. When the Surface is asleep and you click the button, you have it ready almost instantly. Of course if you need to restart or you have shut down the computer, it will take a few seconds to load.</p>
<p><strong>Final thoughts</strong></p>
<p>Of course if you need more power or a bigger screen, you may want to have a look at the Pro version. However if this is going to be your secondary device or you don’t need a super powerful machine, the basic version will do the job.</p>
<p>Let me tell you that one of the things I love the most is the size and weight. I can carry it on my bag (yes it is 600g) but it saves my life wherever I am.</p>
<p>On the down side, and even though some charts give it 10 hours battery life, for me, watching videos, browsing the internet, flipboard, etc I’d say it’s more around 8. Still I think it’s more than enough for most people and definitely beats my work laptop with hardly a couple of hours battery life.</p>
[youtube vPto6XpRq-U]
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/tecnologia/surface-3-killed-my-ipad-and-is-the-coolest-tablet-ever/">Surface 3 killed my iPad (and is the coolest tablet ever)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>El nuevo MSN para Windows 8</title>
		<link>/microbiablog/tecnologia/el-nuevo-msn-para-windows-8/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 08:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[microbia]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tecnología]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[windows 8]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/microbiablog/?p=806</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Y esto sólo acaba de empezar&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/tecnologia/el-nuevo-msn-para-windows-8/">El nuevo MSN para Windows 8</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe title="YouTube video player" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/TCOb8RnS-gU" frameborder="0" width="560" height="315" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p><em>Y esto sólo acaba de empezar&#8230;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/tecnologia/el-nuevo-msn-para-windows-8/">El nuevo MSN para Windows 8</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Windows 8 &#8211; Are you ready?</title>
		<link>/microbiablog/tecnologia/windows-8-are-you-ready/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 16:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[microbia]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tecnología]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/microbiablog/?p=775</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>I am ready and very proud!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/tecnologia/windows-8-are-you-ready/">Windows 8 &ndash; Are you ready?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe title="YouTube video player" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/PRrQM0_9lM0?rel=0" frameborder="0" width="560" height="315" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p><em>I am ready and very proud!</em> <img class="wlEmoticon wlEmoticon-smile" style="border-top-style: none; border-left-style: none; border-bottom-style: none; border-right-style: none" alt="Smile" src="/microbiablog/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/wlEmoticon-smile.png" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/tecnologia/windows-8-are-you-ready/">Windows 8 &ndash; Are you ready?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nuevo logo para Microsoft</title>
		<link>/microbiablog/tecnologia/nuevo-logo-para-microsoft/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 11:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[microbia]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tecnología]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/microbiablog/?p=772</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>¡Qué emoción!!!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/tecnologia/nuevo-logo-para-microsoft/">Nuevo logo para Microsoft</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe height="315" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/OzkZWvAJUr0?rel=0" frameborder="0" width="560" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe>  </p>
<p><em>¡Qué emoción!!!</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/tecnologia/nuevo-logo-para-microsoft/">Nuevo logo para Microsoft</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kin, el tel&#233;fono de Microsoft</title>
		<link>/microbiablog/moviles/kin-el-telfono-de-microsoft/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 21:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[microbia]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[móviles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/microbiablog/moviles/kin-el-telfono-de-microsoft/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cuando no se ha cumplido ni un mes de la presentación de Windows Phone 7, Microsoft lanza ahora Kin, un teléfono que desde luego a mi me ha sorprendido. No ya por el teléfono en sí, sino por el cambio de enfoque de la compañía de Redmond. Y es que hace un par de semanas [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/moviles/kin-el-telfono-de-microsoft/">Kin, el tel&eacute;fono de Microsoft</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cuando no se ha cumplido ni un mes de la presentación de Windows Phone 7, Microsoft lanza ahora <strong>Kin</strong>, un teléfono que desde luego a mi me ha sorprendido. No ya por el teléfono en sí, sino por el cambio de <em>enfoque</em> de la compañía de Redmond.</p>
<p> <span id="more-703"></span>  </p>
<p><img style="border-right-width: 0px; display: block; float: none; border-top-width: 0px; border-bottom-width: 0px; margin-left: auto; border-left-width: 0px; margin-right: auto" title="4521179895_9426a0fed1_o[1]" border="0" alt="4521179895_9426a0fed1_o[1]" src="/microbiablog/wp-content/uploads/2010/04/4521179895_9426a0fed1_o1.jpg" width="500" height="318" /> </p>
<p>Y es que hace un par de semanas estaba reflexionando sobre el problema de no controlar toda la cadena. Al contrario que <strong>Apple</strong>, que <strong>controla desde el concepto</strong>, diseño, fabricación, hasta el punto de venta o el <strong>servicio postventa</strong>, <strong>Microsoft</strong> se encuentra con el problema de <strong>desarrollar un software que tiene que funcionar en distintos dispositivos</strong>, unos <em>touch</em>, con distinta potencia, capacidad… y lo difícil que es sacar el máximo partido al sistema operativo con tantas dependencias.</p>
<p>Sin embargo con Kin, aunque el hardware es de Sharp, Microsoft sabe qué dispositivo utilizará el software y pueden <em>pulir</em> mejor la experiencia de usuario. Además han diseñado una versión específica para estos dispositivos,<strong> dando mayor importancia al aspecto social</strong> del teléfono a través de un interfaz sencillo que facilita estas funciones.</p>
<p>Además estos dispositivos vendrán con la <strong>experiencia</strong> <strong>Zune</strong>: incluyendo música, vídeo, radio y reproductor de podcast. También se integra Zune Pass, acceso a música bajo demanda a través de una suscripción mensual.</p>
<p>Su<strong> llegada a nuestro país</strong> se espera el próximo <strong>otoño</strong>, de la mano de Vodafone. Me gusta el modelo Two, si la experiencia de usuario es buena, y además está bien integrado con Exchange, quizá me pida uno…</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/moviles/kin-el-telfono-de-microsoft/">Kin, el tel&eacute;fono de Microsoft</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 reglas para crear una buena presentaci&#243;n</title>
		<link>/microbiablog/herramientas/5-reglas-para-crear-una-buena-presentacin/</link>
		<comments>/microbiablog/herramientas/5-reglas-para-crear-una-buena-presentacin/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 19:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[microbia]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Herramientas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[office]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[office 2010]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[powerpoint]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/microbiablog/herramientas/5-reglas-para-crear-una-buena-presentacin/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Este vídeo no sólo te desvela las claves para una buena presentación, sino que además muestra el potencial del nuevo motor de movimiento de Powerpoint 2010. Olvídate de las aburridas cortinillas y como diría el mismisimo Steve Jobs: “ensaya, ensaya, ensaya”. Visto en Istartedsomething.com</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/herramientas/5-reglas-para-crear-una-buena-presentacin/">5 reglas para crear una buena presentaci&oacute;n</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Este vídeo no sólo te desvela las claves para una buena presentación, sino que además muestra el potencial del nuevo motor de movimiento de Powerpoint 2010.</p>
<p align="center"><object width="400" height="300"><param name="allowfullscreen" value="true" /><param name="allowscriptaccess" value="always" /><param name="movie" value="http://vimeo.com/moogaloop.swf?clip_id=8021694&amp;server=vimeo.com&amp;show_title=1&amp;show_byline=1&amp;show_portrait=0&amp;color=00adef&amp;fullscreen=1" /><embed src="http://vimeo.com/moogaloop.swf?clip_id=8021694&amp;server=vimeo.com&amp;show_title=1&amp;show_byline=1&amp;show_portrait=0&amp;color=00adef&amp;fullscreen=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" allowfullscreen="true" allowscriptaccess="always" width="400" height="300"></embed></object></p>
<p>Olvídate de las aburridas cortinillas y como diría el mismisimo Steve Jobs: “ensaya, ensaya, ensaya”.</p>
<p>Visto en <a href="http://www.istartedsomething.com/20091207/powerpoint-2010s-five-rules-sample-presentation/" target="_blank">Istartedsomething.com</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/herramientas/5-reglas-para-crear-una-buena-presentacin/">5 reglas para crear una buena presentaci&oacute;n</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/microbiablog/herramientas/5-reglas-para-crear-una-buena-presentacin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Officetab a&#241;ade pesta&#241;as a Office 2007</title>
		<link>/microbiablog/herramientas/officetab-aade-pestaas-a-office-2007/</link>
		<comments>/microbiablog/herramientas/officetab-aade-pestaas-a-office-2007/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 19:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[microbia]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Herramientas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[minipost]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[office]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/microbiablog/herramientas/officetab-aade-pestaas-a-office-2007/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Ahora puedes añadir pestañas a Office 2007 (word, excel y powerpoint) con OfficeTab y trabajar más fácilmente cuando tienes varios documentos abiertos. via DownloadSquad</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/herramientas/officetab-aade-pestaas-a-office-2007/">Officetab a&ntilde;ade pesta&ntilde;as a Office 2007</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ahora puedes añadir pestañas a Office 2007 (word, excel y powerpoint) con <a href="http://hi.baidu.com/officecm" target="_blank">OfficeTab</a> y trabajar más fácilmente cuando tienes varios documentos abiertos. via <a href="http://www.downloadsquad.com/2009/08/24/officetab-adds-tabs-to-word-excel-and-powerpoint/" target="_blank">DownloadSquad</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/herramientas/officetab-aade-pestaas-a-office-2007/">Officetab a&ntilde;ade pesta&ntilde;as a Office 2007</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/microbiablog/herramientas/officetab-aade-pestaas-a-office-2007/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Windows Live Movie Maker</title>
		<link>/microbiablog/herramientas/windows-live-movie-maker/</link>
		<comments>/microbiablog/herramientas/windows-live-movie-maker/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 16:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[microbia]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Herramientas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[edición vídeo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[movie maker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[windows]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/microbiablog/herramientas/windows-live-movie-maker/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Ya está disponible la nueva versión del software de edición de video de Microsoft. Movie Maker os resultará familiar ya que se incluye en Windows, sin embargo en esta nueva versión se incluyen funcionalidades que se echaban en falta y que lo hacen mucho más completo. Lo que más llama la atención es el nuevo [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/herramientas/windows-live-movie-maker/">Windows Live Movie Maker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ya está disponible la nueva versión del software de edición de video de Microsoft. Movie Maker os resultará familiar ya que se incluye en Windows, sin embargo en esta nueva versión se incluyen funcionalidades que se echaban en falta y que lo hacen mucho más completo.<img style="display: block; float: none; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto" src="http://farm3.static.flickr.com/2556/3853069036_33c070e537.jpg" /></p>
<p> <span id="more-599"></span>  </p>
<p>Lo que más llama la atención es el nuevo interfaz, movie maker adopta el <strong>menú de office</strong>, el <em>ribbon</em>, donde todo está ahora más a mano. En la izquierda tenemos el visor con la vista preliminar del vídeo y en la derecha podemos ver el <em>storyboard</em> con los fotogramas y la música que hayamos seleccionado. Gracias al zoom (el icono de la lupa abajo a la derecha) podremos elegir el nivel de detalle del story que queramos.</p>
<p>Hacer una película rápidamente con nuestras fotos es muy sencillo la opción <strong>AutoMovie</strong>. Selecciona una canción, selecciona las fotos y Movie Maker ajustará automáticamente la duración con la de la música, aunque siempre podremos modificarlo manualmente si no estamos contentos.</p>
<p>Otra mejora es en cuanto a la <strong>inserción de texto</strong>. En la antigua versión teníamos que recurrir al asistente de títulos, créditos y subtítulos, que no era nada práctico. Ahora tan sólo tenemos que insertar el texto y podremos controlar fácilmente los efectos, duración… etc.</p>
<p>No hay muchos cambios en cuanto a <strong>efectos y transiciones</strong>, pero suficiente variedad para los videos caseros.</p>
<p>En cuanto al formato, Movie Maker importa <strong>casi todos los formatos de fotos y vídeo</strong> más comunes, pero <strong>sólo graba en WMV</strong> aunque ahora puedes elegir la calidad: 1080p (Full HD), 720p (DVD &#8211; HD Ready), 640&#215;480, o 320×240 además de poder publicar y subir automáticamente tus vídeos a YouTube.</p>
<p>En definitiva, un programa muy completo que nada tiene que envidiar a productos de pago similares y que cubre perfectamente las necesidades del usuario no profesional.</p>
<p>La nueva versión requiere Windows Vista o Windows 7.</p>
<p>Descarga <a href="http://download.live.com/moviemaker" target="_blank">WL Movie Maker</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/herramientas/windows-live-movie-maker/">Windows Live Movie Maker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/microbiablog/herramientas/windows-live-movie-maker/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple rechaza la aplicaci&#243;n Google Voice para iPhone</title>
		<link>/microbiablog/moviles/apple-rechaza-google-voice-para-iphone/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 12:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[microbia]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[móviles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/microbiablog/moviles/apple-rechaza-la-aplicacin-google-voice-para-iphone/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Google Voice, es una aplicación que te permite unificar varios números de teléfono en uno sólo y escuchar los mensajes de voz, pero además en Estados Unidos permite realizar llamadas gratis. Obviamente funcionalidades con las que las operadoras de telefonía no se sentirían nada cómodas, y que ponía en una posición muy difícil a Apple [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/moviles/apple-rechaza-google-voice-para-iphone/">Apple rechaza la aplicaci&oacute;n Google Voice para iPhone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Google Voice, es una aplicación que te permite unificar varios números de teléfono en uno sólo y escuchar los mensajes de voz, pero además en Estados Unidos permite realizar llamadas gratis. Obviamente funcionalidades con las que las operadoras de telefonía no se sentirían nada cómodas, y que ponía en una posición muy difícil a Apple que finalmente ha terminado retirándola de la AppStore. Me pregunto que diría la comisión europea sobre esto si en vez de Apple fuese Microsoft…</p>
<p><strong>ACTUALIZACIÓN 29/07 18:30:</strong> Parece que el autor de la aplicación no se ha dado por vencido y la ha puesto <a href="http://www.modmyi.com/forums/iphone-news/678991-gv-mobile-now-cydia-modmyi-repo.html" target="_blank">disponible gratis en Cydia</a> (el instalador de aplicaciones alternativo a AppStore para usuarios con iphones <em>jailbrakeados</em>.</p>
<p>Via <a href="http://bitelia.com/2009/07/apple-dice-no-a-google-voice-en-la-appstore" target="_blank">Bitelia</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/moviles/apple-rechaza-google-voice-para-iphone/">Apple rechaza la aplicaci&oacute;n Google Voice para iPhone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Traducir conversaciones de Messenger con TBot</title>
		<link>/microbiablog/herramientas/traducir-conversaciones-de-messenger-con-tbot/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[microbia]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Herramientas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[messenger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[traduccion]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/microbiablog/herramientas/traducir-conversaciones-de-messenger-con-tbot/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>TBot es un robot de Messenger que te ayuda a comunicarte en otros idiomas. Simplemente añade Tbot a tus contactos: mtbot@hotmail.com, selecciona el idioma que necesitas y él traducirá al idioma que quieras. Cuando estés hablando con alguien, simplemente añadelo a la conversación y traducirá lo que diga tu amigo. Podeis ver las instrucciones paso [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/herramientas/traducir-conversaciones-de-messenger-con-tbot/">Traducir conversaciones de Messenger con TBot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img style="display: inline; margin-left: 0px; margin-right: 0px" align="right" src="http://farm3.static.flickr.com/2208/3610422121_98cf68c2bb_o.jpg" /> TBot es un robot de Messenger que te ayuda a comunicarte en otros idiomas. Simplemente añade Tbot a tus contactos: <a href="mailto:mtbot@hotmail.com"><strong><em>mtbot@hotmail.com</em></strong></a>, selecciona el idioma que necesitas y él traducirá al idioma que quieras. Cuando estés hablando con alguien, simplemente añadelo a la conversación y traducirá lo que diga tu amigo.</p>
<p>Podeis ver las instrucciones paso a paso y un ejemplo de su funcionamiento en <a href="http://www.makeuseof.com/tag/how-to-auto-translate-foreign-languages-in-msn/" target="_blank">MakeUseOf</a>.</p>
<p>ATENCIÓN: El Bot se encuentra en fase Alpha y las traducciones no son muy precisas, más bien traduce palabra por palabra, por lo que puede ayudarte a entender por donde va la conversación, pero dependiendo del idioma, puede que te deje un poco perdido. El <a href="http://www.microsofttranslator.com/Default.aspx" target="_blank">traductor de Bing</a> funciona muchísimo mejor.</p>
<p>Via <a href="http://www.makeuseof.com/tag/how-to-auto-translate-foreign-languages-in-msn/" target="_blank">Make Use Of</a> | <a href="http://wltbot.spaces.live.com/default.aspx?sa=17048896" target="_blank">Blog de TBot</a> | <a href="http://www.microsofttranslator.com/Default.aspx" target="_blank">Traductor de Bing</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/herramientas/traducir-conversaciones-de-messenger-con-tbot/">Traducir conversaciones de Messenger con TBot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/microbiablog/">microbiablog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
